作词 : Patawawa/Tez Cadey
作曲 : Tez Cadey
Sun’s off
She won’t budge
Down the jungle on her knees
We’ll go
To where we know
Tame the wine drops, stumble down the hills
You got to close your eyes and let them fly, you got to
Drink your tears and sing your fears
Listen to the rumble over rain
And as the flames burned down
We ran ourselves to hide
And heard the words they cried:
He-e-ey
Don’t you run don’t you move until they see
We’re made of dust and ivory
Sun’s off
A child asleep
Swings the ashes to the sea
Will they
Remember me
As the creatures live on peacefully
You got to close your eyes and let them fly， you got to
Drink your tears and sing your fears
Listen to the rumble over pain
And as the flames burned down
We looked the otherside
And heard the way they lied:
He-e-ey
Don’t you run don’t you move until they see
We’re made of dust and ivory
He-e-ey
Don’t you run don’t you move until they see
We’re made of dust and ivory